Nguyen Hoang Long

PHP Backend Developer

💄 Male

🖹 Jan 24, 2001

Q 0965 286 066

■ longnh.2401@gmail.com

Tan Binh District, Ho Chi Minh City

OBJECTIVE -

I'm a developer with over a year of experience in website development. In which most of the time I use PHP and JavaScript for work. I enjoy spending my time creating landing page, section and learning new technologies, new knowledge to become a full-stack developer professional in the next 4-5 years.

SKILLS

Programming Languages

PHP, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Frameworks/Platforms/Database/Other

- Laravel, VueJS
- · Bootstrap, jQuery
- MySQL
- Apache JMeter, OWASP® Zed Attack Proxy (ZAP)
- Wordpress
- Adobe photoshop CS6, Figma

Soft skill

- Ability to work in groups with 10+ members
- Problem solving skills
- · Withstand high pressure environment
- Always maintain a positive attitude that is a benefit to any situation.

WORK EXPERIENCE -

Ethan Technology Asia Co., Ltd

December 2021 - Now

E-COMMERCE WEBSITE SYSTEM - DEVELOPER

- Description: An e-commerce Web system creates an online shop and management system for customers
- Technologies:

• Front-end: Using Nuxt.js framework on server side rendering

Back-end: Laravel

• Responsibilities:

- Handle backend and frontend tasks
- Write test code, testcase
- Test, optimize performance
- Review, test, support members in team
- Optimize file automation build docker in local

Cloud Nine Solutions Co., Ltd

July 2021 - Sep 2021

E-COMMERCE WEBSITE DEMO - INTERN

• Description: An e-commerce Web demo made with 2 other members

• Technologies:

• Front-end: Using VueJS framework

Back-end: LaravelMobile: Flutter

• Responsibilities:

- Handle backend, frontend and mobile tasks
- Requirement analysis, database design, use case diagram drawing
- · Deploy website to the server using nginx
- Other: Research and report, the following keywords: API, RESTFUL API, API Document, Vuejs, Laravel, Flutter, Nginx,...

EDUCATION

Sep 2019 - Dec 2021

FPT POLYTECHNIC COLLEGE

Major: Web Programming

GPA: 7.8/10

HONORS & AWARDS

20-01-2020

Good student in Fall 2020 at school

© topcv.vn